Huh?
Shampoo!
Ranma, you're dead.
The Chinese Amazons
are a very proud people.
Losing to an outsider
is a dishonor worse than death.
The Kiss of Death is a solemn vow,
one that requires her to chase you down
to the depths of hell
in pursuit of killing you.
And don't come in someone's house
to pick a fight!
Well, that's no good.
Poor girl.
I guess this means
she ended up losing a second time.
This was all an accident
and you did not lose.
Liar!
Now accept your Kiss of Death
with some dignity.
Hmm.
Mmm, mmm?
RANMA1/2
YOU I LOVE
Ah.
What could be causing all this racket?
Oh, Dad, it's you.
Well, to be honest, I'm not really sure
what's going on here.
Ranma's ex-lover from China came over,
broke into the house
and started demanding
that they get back together.
His ex-lover?
If you're feeling that flustered,
you shouldn't go rattling your mouth off!
Although it is surprisingly accurate,
isn't it?
This has been the first time
she's ever seen me in my male form.
Well if that's the case,
you two seem pretty close.
What's your relationship with Shampoo?
Aiyaa.
Akane, listen to me.
What do you want?
Do whatever you want then.
All right. If you're all gonna see me
like that, I guess I can't stop you.
Ranma.
That's the only way we're able to see it.
YEP
Fine, then. Let's call off the engagement!
Ranma and I don't need to get married.
Akane!
- Hey, Shampoo. You gotta get off me.
- Now then, Ranma.
Ah.
Let's hear what pitiful explanation
you have to offer me.
I-I keep trying to tell you,
- I-I have no idea what's going on.
- Poke, poke.
- Huh?
- Hmm?
CHINESE AMAZON SUTRA
Look.
Let's see here. "Laws of Chinese Amazons"...
No! It can't be!
What does the book say?
You idiot!
I don't know how to read Chinese!
If you're gonna yell at me,
you should wait until you stop crying!
"The Laws of the Chinese Amazons."
Nabiki, welcome home.
It's good to have you back.
Uh...
"Should one of our female warriors
ever be defeated by an outsider,
in the case of a female-gendered opponent,
she must receive the Kiss of Death
and then be killed.
However, in the case
of the male-gendered opponent,
you must make him your husband."
What? Huh?
- You're making that up!
- Mmm, mmm.
Do I look like someone
that would joke around about this?
Yes, you do!
Do you even know
how to read Chinese to begin with?
Huh?
- Of course.
- Huh?
Just kidding. I don't know how.
But there is a Japanese translation
in the margin.
Oh, yeah. Look at that!
There it is. I missed it!
Ranma, you moron.
You're an idiot!
Stupid......you are so unbelievable.
You stupid, freaking, idiot!
You stupid Ranma!
I think I feel better.
I know we're engaged, but that was
something our fathers chose for us.
At the end of the day, it's not
like we actually liked each other.
Listen up! Akane is already engaged to me.
And if you touch her again, I'll kill you.
Hmm.
- J-Just listen to me, Shampoo.
- Hmm?
It's the modern day.
You can't have laws
that make you kill women who best you
and you can't require
that a man has to marry you either.
Those sorts of laws
are just outdated nonsense.
There are laws?
So, in a nutshell...
The textbook definition of trapping a man.
Where did you two come from?
So what do you say to making up
with Ranma? Well, Akane?
And let's be real,
do you think that Ranma has the ability
to get a girlfriend on his own?
What do you say? Do you get it?
Mm-hmm.
Wo de ai ren.
You didn't get any of that, did you?
Let's check out "Wo de ai ren."
This says it means "my husband."
What I'm trying to say is...
I'm not really interested in
being in a relationship with...
...you?
Wo ai ni.
I'm trying to tell you
there's nothing between the two of us.
And, really, who cares if there is a law
because I'm definitely not m-marrying you.
I mean, it'd be ridiculous
to do something like that...
- Let's see if "Wo ai ni" is listed.
- ...not to mention old-fashioned...
- Yeah, it's right there.
- ...inappropriate...
- It means "I love you."
- ...a second to think about it.
Why do they have to be so loud?
So anyway, like I was trying to tell you,
I just think that... I think we should take
more time to learn
about each other.
I'm not a fan of the idea of marrying
someone I don't even
know...
Oh, dear. Look at how wound up he is.
It's fun watching them, huh, Aka...
Ai ren!
LISTEN TO YOURSELF, DOLT!
I don't think I noticed it before because
she was trying to kill me the whole time...
Wo ai ni.
...but Shampoo is actually pretty cute.
I wish Akane was
as up-front as Shampoo is.
That's cold!
You know, earlier today...
...when I saw Akane
getting jealous over you...
...it really hurt my freaking feelings!
You moron. Why would I care about that?
You might as well stick around as a girl
and then Shampoo can come back
- and beat you up.
- Argh!
Well, I hope that you get stuck as a pig
and then eaten by Akane!
Don't call me a pig!
Pig.
That's right. I almost forgot!
Your name is P-chan, isn't it?
Why, you...
I think you should take a dip
and cool off.
Ha!
That's what you get.
'Cause we both know, it's not
like Akane has any reason to be jealous...
Uh-oh.
Oh, I'm not upset. Why would I be?
I mean, just think about it.
It's not like the two of us
are engaged anymore.
Um, well, what I was saying was...
You two are more than welcome
to go ahead and get to know each other!
P-chan, come on.
Ak-kane?
I'll kill you!
Hey, can we talk this out first?
You gotta give me a br--
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Wait! W-w-wait...
You're really dangerous!
Would you please cut it out?
I'll kill you!
So it seems to me,
when he's a boy she wants him,
but when he's a girl,
she just wants him dead.
I'll kill you!
Yeah, those two need to learn
more about each other
before they get into a relationship.
I'll kill you!
Stupid Ranma.
ANYTHING GOES
MARTIAL ARTS TENDO DOJO
P-chan, where are you?
I guess P-chan must have run off again.
Oh! Hello, Akane.
Would you mind going to wake up Ranma?
And why do I have to do it?
No specific reason.
You've got a death grip on that grudge.
Still mad about Ranma and Shampoo?
No, I'm not.
Akane.
What do you say we try being a little more
up-front with our feelings for a while?
What do you mean?
She's scary!
- I was scared!
- It's okay, Papa. You'll be all right.
There's nothing for you to cry about.
Ranma, how late are you sleeping in?
Wo de ai ren.
Cold!
What the hell was that for, Akane?
You tryin' to fight this early, you--
Wo de ai ren.
Shampoo,
what are you doing in my bed?
- Hmm.
- Hmm?
I'll kill you!
I wish I knew what your problem was!
Oh, my. I didn't realize Shampoo was here.
Hmm?
Let me be clear.
I had no idea Shampoo snuck into my bed.
Hmm, that's funny.
I don't remember asking.
It's too early for that anyway.
You really are determined
not to listen to people.
I mean, you cuddle the pig
while you're sleeping, right?
What does P-chan have to do with this?
Only an idiot feels
like they're competing with a pig.
Yeah, right. Like anyone
would get jealous over you anyway.
So sorry!
My hand must have slipped.
You know this is why
you're never gonna be cute.
I already told you I'm fine with that.
Akane.
My next journey calls,
so I'm leaving without saying goodbye.
I can see now that I'm just your pet.
I'll never be more than P-chan to you.
We know
that Ranma's infidelity hurts Akane.
If we're gonna home-wreck,
now's the time to do it.
Do you hear yourself?
Shut your halo!
I want you to remember
what Ranma's done to you.
Why do you think it is that Akane
only sees you as a pet in the first place?
Now's the time
for you to take your chance.
No, that wouldn't be right.
I bet if you can be patient enough,
that girl from China
will just end up killing Ranma anyway.
Let that moment be your chance.
That's way more nefarious than my idea!
What need is there
to get your own hands dirty?
Good things come to those who wait.
But I...
Interrupt them now,
so you can strike while the iron's hot.
No, it's far too early for you to act.
Calm down!
I'm so sorry, Ryoga.
Because what I feel
for Ranma is love.
If something like that were to happen,
my oh-too-fragile heart
would shatter into tiny pieces.
Farewell, Akane.
Hmm.
I thought we'd never make it to lunch.
I'm so hungry.
- Huh?
- That can't be good.
What in the...
- Does it sound like it's getting closer?
- Hmm?
Hmm?
Hello, male Ranma.
Shampoo, are you serious right now?
What the hell do you want?
I made you a bento box.
- Hmm?
P-chan!
Huh?
What do you think you're doing?
- Um, uh...
- Say "ah."
Hey, hey.
Wake up, hey!
Ow!
Oh, you're okay, P-chan.
Huh?
No.
The Kiss of Death?
So it's like that.
I won't back down.
I accept your challenge.
Hey, now, the pig is alive
so why don't we all just calm down?
No more!
After everything she's done to me,
I'm gonna settle this.
Doesn't anything get through
to that thick head of yours?
You don't stand a chance
at beating Shampoo--
You're the one with a thick head.
- Watch out!
- What?
'Kay, P-chan. You should be safe here.
I'm gonna be fine. Don't worry about me.
The Kiss of Death.
I'll hunt you down to the depths of hell,
and kill you.
Oh, don't worry.
'Cause I'm not going anywhere.
I'm putting an end to this here.
Hey! Hey! You all right?
Oh, man.
Guess the ball must have popped him
pretty good.
Akane!
She already went through there.
What the hell?
Akane.
Akane!
Akane! Akane! Akane!
Whoa.
Akane!
Ryoga.
Hey.
Hey, come on, wake up!
Akane!
Huh?
What happened?
You're up? You idiot!
That's why I told you not to do it.
Hmm?
Ak-kane?
Do I know you?
Hmm?